Guide to the Danbury Preservation Trust Records MS 039
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
- Series II: Events
  - Exhibits
    - Future of the Past newspaper supplement, 1983 (Map-case OS Drawer 3, Folder 2)
      The Future of the Past DNT supplement 5/11/1983
  - School Projects
    - Eye Spy Contest forms, photos, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      Eye Spy Danbury contest forms, original photos glued to paper
    - Seventh grade project - Study of Local Architecture, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
      7th grade architectural Projects - worksheets, instructions
    - Danbury Tricentennial Pursuit, 1985 (Box OS 1, Folder 3)
      Danbury Tercentennial Pursuit (board game) created by Danbury Public Schools Gifted program
  - Walking Tours
    - Main St. walking tour, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      11 photos in indivual envelopes and negatives of Oct. walking tour and lecture
    - Danburians remember "the floods of 1955", 1995 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      Walking tour and slide show flyers, DNT article
    - Deer Hill Avenue tour materials, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 7-8)
      Correspondence - Deer Hill Ave. walking tour planning, copy of old Deer Hill photo; DNT "Modern Living" section article on Deer Hill Victorian homes.
    - Miscellaneous materials on walking tours, 1976-1986 (Box 5, Folder 11-12)
      Deer Hill Ave, Main St., Wooster Square, Flood area tour and talk flyer, publicaton pages on Hartford walking tour - self-guided, copy of old Danbury city hall artist drawing, brochure for walk through history, flyers for 1980 exhibit of Roger Baldwin photographs; flyers for non-Danbury tours, Main St. Walk Through History and Wooster Square materials, copies of historic resources inventory sheets for Main St. buldings, copies of DNT articles on buildings, Tri-centiennial house tour, Elmwood Park, DNT article from "Modern Living" section on Tri-Centnnial tour,
    - Danbury Bicentennial Homes Tour, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 10A)
      Danbury Bicentennial Homes 1976 - 1996 booklet complied by the Danbury Bicentennial Homes Committee
- Series III: Projects
  - Historic Districts
    - Long Ridge historic district proposal, undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
      Long Ridge Historic District
    - Main Street proposal- Connecticut Historical Commission materials, 1979-1983 (Box 5, Folder 25-27)
      Connecticut Historical Commission correspondence - historic district, letters apealing decision of the Commission, map of properties included, guidelines for questions and answers for owners, historic preservation grants materials, procedural guildelines document - State Preservtion officer, report by William Devlin on Main Street Historic District Proposal, pictures glued to paper, proposal for Balmforth- Maple Ave. survey, 1980; Historical district document from Connecticut Historical Commission; packet of information for building owners
    - Main Street nomination forms for the Nation Register of Historic Places w/ correspondence, 1983-1988 (Box 5, Folder 22-24)
      Nomination forms for Main St. Historic District, copies of materials sent to property owners describing intent of nomination, photocopies of Main St. historic district buildings, some interiors also (note that negatives on file with Conn. Hist. Com.), National Register of Historic Places flyer
    - Main Street maps, undated (Box OS 1, Folder 5)
      National Historic District - Main St. maps in folder
  - Historic Resources Inventory
    - Phase I - Main St. Survey - inventory index, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 41)
      1980 Historic resources inventory, typewritten
    - Phase I - Main St. Survey, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 42)
      Inventory sheets for1 to 46 Main street buildings, photocopies of building pictures
    - Phase I - Main St. Survey, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 43)
      Inventory sheets for 47 to 75 Main street buildings, photocopies of building pictures
    - Phase I - Main St. Survey, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 44)
      Inventory sheets for 80 to 137-9 Main street buildings, photocopies of building pictures
    - Phase I - Main St. Survey, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 45)
      Inventory sheets for 141 to 209-11 Main street buildings, photocopies of building pictures
    - Phase I - Main St. Survey, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 46)
      Inventory sheets for 210 to 254 Main street buildings, photocopies of building pictures
    - Phase I - Main St. Survey, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 47)
      Inventory sheets for 257 to 285-7 Main street buildings, photocopies of building pictures
    - Phase I - Main St. Survey, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 48)
      Inventory sheets for 286 1/2 to 348 Main street buildings, photocopies of building pictures
    - Phase I - Main St. Survey, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 49)
      Inventory sheets for 350 to 369 Main street buildings, photocopies of building pictures
    - Phase I - Main St. Survey, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 50)
      Inventory sheets for 370 to 415 Main street buildings, photocopies of building pictures
    - Phase I - Main St. Survey -adjacent to Main, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 51)
      Inventory sheets for 10-11-12 Chapel Place buildings, 2-8 through 60 Elm Street, Ives st. (Railroad Place), 10-12 to 18-22 Liberty Street photocopies of building pictures
    - Phase I - Main St. Survey - adjacent to Main, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 52)
      Inventory sheets for 24-6 to 42-4 Liberty Street, Library Place, Post Office Place, Tower Place, 2-16 to 31 West street, 16 to 32-4 White Street buildings, photocopies of building pictures
    - Phase I - Main St. Survey -grant, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 38-40)
      Connecticut Historical Commission Survey grant, Scott-Fanton loan of $200, request for addiontional funds, expenses, time sheets; costs, State Preservation Officer letter re: survey, copy of funding agreement, fact sheet, instructions; revised survey and grant budget, Janick authorization to get grant ,, draft proposal, State Historic Preservation Officer letter of award
    - Phase II: Balmforth-Maple Corridor Survey - miscellaeous materials, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 53)
      Survey contract, map, list of McLachlan employees, copies of street Guide pages, Patch St. Bridge history, photocopies of pictures
    - Phase II: Balmforth-Maple Corridor Survey - notes on history, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 54)
      Survey handwritten notes on history of the area - property records information
    - Phase II: Balmforth-Maple Corridor Survey - Crosby, E. Franklin, North, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 57)
      Crosby St, E. Franklin, North St. - handwritten notes - property records, Tweedy Silk Mills history [hat bands]
    - Phase II: Balmforth-Maple Corridor Survey - Maple, Barnum Court, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 58)
      Maple Ave., Barnum Court property records, obituary of Arnold Turner, cites to News Times articles, Wooster Cemetary Notes
    - Phase II: Balmforth-Maple Corridor Survey - Maple, Patch, Thorpe, Union, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 59)
      Maple Ave, Patch St., Thorpe St., Union Handwritten notes - property records
    - Phase II: Balmforth-Maple Corridor Survey - report, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 60)
      Maple - Balmforth Survey report, copy of Balmforth - Maple Ave. Corridor survey report
    - Phase II: Balmforth-Maple Corridor Survey - index and contact sheets, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 61)
      Photo proofs and list of buildings Balmforth - Maple Ave. corridor
    - Phase II: Balmforth-Maple Corridor Survey - Balmforth, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 55-56)
      Balmforth Ave. handwritten notes from property records
    - Phase II: Balmforth-Maple Corridor Survey - Balmforth, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      Copies of historic resources inventory pages for 4 - 36-38 Balmforth
    - Phase II: Balmforth-Maple Corridor Survey - Balmforth, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      Copies of historic resources inventory pages - 37 - 53 Balmforth Ave.
    - Phase II: Balmforth-Maple Corridor Survey - Balmforth, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      Copies of historic resources inventory pages 54 - 91 Balmforth Ave. bridge (with separate bridge pictures)
    - Phase II: Balmforth-Maple Corridor Survey - Barnum Court, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      Barnum Court history, Barnum Court historic inventory pages
    - Phase II: Balmforth-Maple Corridor Survey - Crosby, E. Franklin, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      Crosby St. history, Crosby St. historic inventory pages, East Franklin St. history and historic inventory pages with pictures of bridge, copy of Tweedy Silk Mills history
    - Phase II: Balmforth-Maple Corridor Survey - North St., 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      North St. history and historic inventory pages 6 - 67-69 North St, separate pictures of North St. bridge
    - Phase II: Balmforth-Maple Corridor Survey - Maple Ave., 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      Maple Ave. history, maple Ave. historic inventory pages
    - Phase II: Balmforth-Maple Corridor Survey - Patch St., 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      Patch St. History, historic inventory pages
    - Phase II: Balmforth-Maple Corridor Survey, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      Thorpe St. history and historic inventory pages, Union Ave. history and inventory pages, Inventory sheets for 42, 46-52, 76, and 40 White St.
    - Phase III: Elm and New Streets Neighborhood Survey - Montgomery, Elm and DPT materials, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      Original contract, DPT meeting minutes 12/9/81, Montgomery St and Elm St. handwritten notes ownership history
    - Phase III: Elm and New Streets Neighborhood Survey - Montgomery, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      Montgomery St. handwritten notes
    - Phase III: Elm and New Streets Neighborhood Survey - New St., 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 14)
      New St. handwritten notes ownership history
    - Phase III: Elm and New Streets Neighborhood Survey - Stevens St., 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 18)
      Stevens St. handwritten notes
    - Phase III: Elm and New Streets Neighborhood Survey - miscellaneous notes, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 19)
      Notes from directory for Beaver,Elm, Montgomery, New, Stevens and Spring Sts, hand drawn maps
    - Phase III: Elm and New Streets Neighborhood Survey - New St., Stevens St., 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      Hand written notes for New St., 4 Stevens St.
    - Phase III: Elm and New Streets Neighborhood Survey - Spring St., 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      Handwritten notes South side of Spring St. 4 - 52.
    - Phase III: Elm and New Streets Neighborhood Survey - Stevens St., 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 22)
      Stevens St. hand written notes 608, 10, 14, 18. ownership history
    - Phase III: Elm and New Streets Neighborhood Survey - Spring St., Elm St., 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 23)
      North side of Spring St. 23 - 37; south side Elm St 94 - 104 - 104 1/2 handwritten notes ownership history
    - Phase III: Elm and New Streets Neighborhood Survey, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 24)
      South side of Stevens St. 20-22 to 46, Stebbins family history, Mrs. Dickens article, relation of Stuards, 111 West St. notes, notes on Starr family from Starr geneology at Danbury Library
    - Phase III: Elm and New Streets Neighborhood Survey - Stevens St., 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 25)
      North side of Stevens St. nos. 15 - 45. handwritten notes
    - Phase III: Elm and New Streets Neighborhood Survey - Stevens St., New St., 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 26)
      Stevens St. 5 -11; New Street 34 to 42, handwritten notes ownership history
    - Phase III: Elm and New Streets Neighborhood Survey - Spring St., Elm St., 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 27)
      Spring St. 15 - 21; Elm St. 82 - 92; handwritten notes [includes ownership history of the Octagon house]
    - Phase III: Elm and New Streets Neighborhood Survey - Spring St., Elm St., 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 28)
      5-7 to 11-13 Spring St., 68-70 to 80 Elm St., hand wirtten notes ownership history
    - Phase III: Elm and New Streets Neighborhood Survey Spring, Beaver, Elm, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 29)
      39 to 47 Spring St., 25-29 to 37 Beaver St., 106 to 114 Elm St. handwritten notes ownership history
    - Phase III: Elm and New Streets Neighborhood Survey report, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 30)
      Copy of report Historical and architectural resources survey Elm - New Streets neighborhood
    - Phase III: Elm and New Streets Neighborhood Survey - Elm St., 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 31)
      Historic resources inventory sheets - Elm St. (pictures attached)
    - Phase III: Elm and New Streets Neighborhood Survey - Montgomery St., 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 32)
      Historic resources inventory sheets Montgomery St. (pictures attached)
    - Phase III: Elm and New Streets Neighborhood Survey -New St, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 33)
      New St. historic resources inventory sheets with pictures
    - Phase III: Elm and New Streets Neighborhood Survey - Spring St., 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 34)
      Spring St. historic inventory sheets with pictures 4 to 22
    - Phase III: Elm and New Streets Neighborhood Survey - Spring St., 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 35)
      Spring St historic inventory sheets with pictures 23 to 52
    - Phase III: Elm and New Streets Neighborhood Survey Stevens, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 36)
      Stevens St. historic inventory sheets with pictures 4 to 29
    - Phase III: Elm and New Streets Neighborhood Survey -Stevens St, West St., 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 37)
      Stevens St. historic inventory sheets with pictures 30 to 48 (called 111 West St)
    - Phase III: Elm and New Streets Neighborhood Survey - Elm St., 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 11-12)
      copies of maps, Elm St. assessors cards; Elm St. handwritten notes
    - Phase III: Elm and New Streets Neighborhood Survey - Spring St., 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 15-17)
      Spring St. handwritten notes; handwritten charts of history of ownership- Spring St., copies of maps of area
    - Phase IV: Town Hill Survey - report and article, 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 38)
      Copy of Town Hill Survey 1982 -1983 report, Renews article on Town Hill v.4 #4 Oct. 1983
    - Phase IV: Town Hill Survey - Center, Clark, Clason, Comstock, 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 39)
      Historic inventory sheets and pictures 21 -35 Center St, 4 - 16 Clark St, 4 Clason Pl., 2 to 31 Comstock St.
    - Phase IV: Town Hill Survey - Cottage, Homeplace, Keeler St., 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 40)
      3 to 34 Cottage St. (includes Sacred Heart Church), 13 to 17 Home Place, 7-13 to 68 Keeler St. historic inventory sheets
    - Phase IV: Town Hill Survey - Liberty St., 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 42)
      Liberty St. historic inventory sheets
    - Phase IV: Town Hill Survey McDermott, Nichols, 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 43)
      McDermott St, Nichols St. historic inventory sheets
    - Phase IV: Town Hill Survey - Pahquioques, Prospect, Sheridan, 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 44)
      Pahquioques Ave, Prospect St, Sheridan St. historic inventory sheets
    - Phase IV: Town Hill Survey - South St, Stillman, Stone, Town Hill, 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 45)
      South St. School, 97 to 135 South St., State Street, Stillman Ave, Stone St., 52 Town Hill Ave. Historic resources inventory sheets,
    - Phase IV: Town Hill Survey - Town Hill, Triangle, 1983-1986 (Box 6, Folder 46)
      7 to 94 Town Hill Ave., 1 and 7 Triangle St historic inventory sheets
    - Phase IV: Town Hill Survey - grant materials, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 47-48)
      Correspondence re: survey with state preservation officer re: grant, contract, budget, map with phases marked on it.
    - Phase IV: Town Hill Survey - Keeler St. pictures, 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 41)
      9 pictures of 34-38 Keeler St. brownstones.
    - Phase V: Deer Hill Avenue Survey - 1983-1984 report, undated (Box 6, Folder 54)
      Deer Hill Ave Suvey report - first installment 1983 -1984, includes Terrace Ave. commentary
    - Phase V: Deer Hill Avenue Survey - 1986 report (Box 6, Folder 55)
      Phase 5 Historic and architectural resources survey of City of Danbury May, 1986 report
    - Phase V: Deer Hill Avenue Survey - maps and prints, undated (Box 6, Folder 56)
      Copies of sections of maps, Danbury - Main St., Wooster ST, Starrs Plain; copies of pictures of Jackson Institute, Trowbridge genealogy
    - Phase V: Deer Hill Avenue Survey - Deer Hill Avenue, 1983-1986 (Box 6, Folder 57)
      Historic resources inventory pages Deer Hill Ave nos. 1 to 97
    - Phase V: Deer Hill Avenue Survey - Deer Hill Ave, Division St., 1983-1986 (Box 6, Folder 58)
      Historic resources inventory pages Deer Hill Ave nos. 98 -to 162, Division St. 5 to 28.
    - Phase V: Deer Hill Avenue Survey - Divison St., Park Ave., Pleasant St., 1983-1986 (Box 6, Folder 59)
      Divison St. 29 to 60, Park Ave. 2 to 106-108, Pleasant St. 4 to 29 historic resources inventory pages
    - Phase V: Deer Hill Avenue Survey - Pleasant St, West Wooster, Terrace Pl., 1983-1986 (Box 6, Folder 60)
      Historic resources inventory pages 33 to 37 Pleasant St., Terrace Place, 5 to 59 West Wooster St.
    - Phase V: Deer Hill Avenue Survey - Cherry, Bank, Boughton, Bennett Place, 1983-1986 (Box 6, Folder 61)
      Assesor's cards notes - Cherry St., Bank St., Bennett Place, Boughton; list of 1884 DNT articles on new houses
    - Phase V: Deer Hill Avenue Survey - Dibble, East Pearl, Foster, 1983-1986 (Box 6, Folder 62)
      Assessor's cards notes Dibble, East Pearl, Foster Sts.
    - Phase V: Deer Hill Avenue Survey - 6- 40 Division, 1983-1986 (Box 6, Folder 63)
      6 to 40 Division St. - assesor's cars notes, handwritten, handwritten ownership histories, handwritten chart of owners
    - Phase V: Deer Hill Avenue Survey - 6-60 Divison St., 1983-1986 (Box 6, Folder 64)
      Handwritten ownership notes and charts 6 to 60 Division St.
    - Phase V: Deer Hill Avenue Survey - 5 - 47 Division, 1983-1986 (Box 6, Folder 65)
      5 to 47 Division St. - layout of streets fromTown Records, architectural evalaution form handwritten ownership histories and charts
    - Phase V: Deer Hill Avenue Survey - background information on streets, undated (Box 6, Folder 66)
      Notes on history of Lincoln Ave., Garfield Ave., Jefferson, Washington, Southern Blvd, Pleasant St, 2 to 4 Division St. - notes and assessor cards information.
    - Phase V: Deer Hill Avenue Survey - grant & survey information, 1979-1985 (Box 6, Folder 49-53)
      1985 contract, 1984 contract, correspondance about grant and suveys, The Foundation center materials, articles, copy of Connecticut Historic Preservation historical and achitectural surveys guide
    - Phase V: Deer Hill Avenue Survey Grand, Harding Pl., 1983-1986 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      Grand St, Harding Place- assesor cards notes
    - Phase V: Deer Hill Avenue Survey - Great Plain, 1983-1986 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      Great Plain Rd. - assessor's cards notes, Danbury News articles, notes from Nichols diaries, census notes
    - Phase V: Deer Hill Avenue Survey - Harmony, Housman, Linden Pl., 1983-1986 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      Harmony St, Housman, Linden Pl - assessor's cards notes, some onwership notes
    - Phase V: Deer Hill Avenue Survey, 1983-1986 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      Mountainville Rd, Mountainville Ave, Pearl
    - Phase V: Deer Hill Avenue Survey, 1983-1986 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      Orchard St. assesor's cards notes and handwritten ownership histories
    - Phase V: Deer Hill Avenue Survey - background information on streets, 1983-1986 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      Notes about Stevens St, George St., Orchard St. - assessor's cards notes, handwritten ownership notes; East Pearl St, William St., Boughton St., Bank St. - assesor cards notes, 21 George St - handwritten history
    - Phase V: Deer Hill Avenue Survey - Orchard St., 1983-1986 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      Orchard St. - assessor's cards notes and handwritten ownership histories
    - Phase V: Deer Hill Avenue Survey, 1983-1986 (Box 7, Folder 13)
      Rowan St. - handwritten ownership notes, map
    - Phase V: Deer Hill Avenue Survey - 68 Sugar Hollow Rd., 1983-1986 (Box 7, Folder 14)
      68 Sugar Hollow Rd. handwritten notes of ownership history
    - Phase V: Deer Hill Avenue Survey - Terrace Pl., 1983-1986 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      Terrace Place - assesor cards notes, handwritten notes, Danbury News articles,
    - Phase V: Deer Hill Avenue Survey - Whitlock, 1983-1986 (Box 7, Folder 16)
      Whitlock - assessor cards notes, some history
    - Phase V: Deer Hill Avenue Survey - William St., 1983-1986 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      William St., - assesor cards notes, some ownership history notes
    - Phase V: Deer Hill Avenue Survey -West St., 1983-1986 (Box 7, Folder 18)
      West St. - assessor's cards notes, copies of pictures: Mountainville Ave., West. St. monument, West St. house: 57 William St. property record sheet, some ownership history, copy of picture of Immanuel Lutheran church interior
    - Phase V: Deer Hill Avenue Survey - Wilson, 1983-1986 (Box 7, Folder 19)
      Wilson - assessor cards notes
    - Phase V: Deer Hill Avenue Survey _ Wooster St, Wooster Heights, 1983-1986 (Box 7, Folder 20)
      Wooster St. (near Main St.), Wooster Heights - assesor cards notes
    - Phase V: Deer Hill Avenue Survey Stadley Rough, 1983-1986 (Box 7, Folder 21)
      Stadley Rough - assessor's cards notes, handwritten ownership notes, map, copies of typewritten ownership notes
    - Phase V: Deer Hill Avenue Survey - Quien, Seeley, Spruce, Parks property, 1983-1986 (Box 7, Folder 22)
      Quien St, (off Pleasant St.), Seeley St., Spruce St (Linden in 1900) - assesor cards notes and some ownership history; Southern Blvd - Tarrywile - Parks property history - Danb. Real estate records and notes,
    - Phase V: Deer Hill Avenue Survey -133 - 157 Deer Hill, 1983-1986 (Box 7, Folder 23)
      133 to 153-157 Deer Hill Ave. - assessor cards notes, maps, city directory pages, census records, Deer Hill budget list
    - Phase V: Deer Hill Avenue Survey - 1-63 Deer Hill, 1983-1986 (Box 7, Folder 24)
      News Times articles - City Directory pages, 1-63 Deer Hill Ave. - assessor's cards notes, Inventory page for #1, handwritten ownership notes
    - Phase V: Deer Hill Avenue Survey - 28-87, 1983-1986 (Box 7, Folder 25)
      28 to 87 Deer Hill Ave. - historic inventory sheets, assessor cards notes, handwritten ownership history notes
    - Phase V: Deer Hill Avenue Survey - 60-90 Deer Hill, 1983-1986 (Box 7, Folder 26)
      60 to 90 Deer Hill Ave. - historic inventory sheets, assessor cards notes, handwritten ownership history notes
    - Phase V: Deer Hill Avenue Survey - 95 to 133,162 Deer Hill, 1983-1986 (Box 7, Folder 29)
      Handwritten map of homes, Deer Hill church and parsonage - article, notes, architectual drawing, history of land ownership; 95 to 133, 162 Deer Hill - notes on ownership history, assessor cards notes
    - Phase V: Deer Hill Avenue Survey - 106-133 Deer Hill, 1983-1986 (Box 7, Folder 30)
      106 to 133 Deer Hill Ave. - handwitten notes on ownership history, assessor cards notes
    - Phase V: Deer Hill Avenue Survey - 130-158 Deer Hill, 1983-1986 (Box 7, Folder 31)
      130 to 158 Deer hill Ave. (some George St. land also), handwritten ownership notes, assessor cards notes, sketches of house placement on land
    - Phase V: Deer Hill Avenue Survey - Divison, Dibble, 1983-1986 (Box 7, Folder 44)
      Historic resources inventory sheets with a few separate photos - Dibble St, Division St. (some photos need sleeves)
    - Phase V: Deer Hill Avenue Survey - 1 - 164 Deer Hill Ave., 1983-1986 (Box 7, Folder 45)
      1 to 164 Deer Hill Ave. - historic resources inventory sheets (some photos need sleeves)
    - Phase V: Deer Hill Avenue Survey - East Pearl, East Starrs Plain, Foster, 1983-1986 (Box 7, Folder 46)
      Historic resources inventory sheets with some separate photos East Pearl St., East Starrs Plain, Foster St.
    - Phase V: Deer Hill Avenue Survey - 49 - 104 Garfield, 1983-1986 (Box 7, Folder 47)